Guide to the Union Label and Service Trades Council of Greater New York and Long Island Records WAG.054
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: Union Label Activities, 1938-1976
  - Dinner - Seventh Annual Greater NY Union Label Award of Merit to Nathan Ehrlich and Vincent D. McDonnell, 9/11/1968 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Dinner - Second Annual LI Union Label Award of Merit to Anthony J. Castaldo and Charles A. Mulligan, 9/8/1967 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Dinner - Third Annual LI Union Label Award of Merit to William C. DeKoning and Edwin E. Regnell Jr., 9/13/1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Dinner - Fourth Annual LI Union Label Award of Merit to R.W. MacGregor, G.M. Levy and L.V. Tempera, 9/4/1969 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Dinner - Eighth Annual Greater NY Union Label Award of Merit to Richard E. Booth and Jack Townsend, 9/10/1969 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Dinner - Ninth Annual Greater NY Union Label Award of Merit to Albert Shanker and James F. Echeandia, 9/9/1970 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Dinner - Fifth Annual LI Union Label Award of Merit to George Favale and Edwin E. Epstein, 9/11/1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Dinner - 60th Anniversary Dinner of the Union Label and Service Trades Council of Greater NY & LI, AFL-CIO, 9/11/1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Dinner - Tenth Annual Greater NY Union Label Award of Merit to Lillian Hecht and Bernard R. Glick, 9/13/1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Dinner - Sixth Annual LI Union Label Award of Merit to Ralph G. Caso and Paul A. Gamaldi, 9/22/1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Dinner - Combined Eleventh Annual Greater NY Union Label and Seventh Annual Long Island Union Label Award of Merit to Transport Workers Union Local 100, 9/19/1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Dinner - Twelfth Annual Greater NY Union Label Awards of Merit to Dolores Drapala and Alice F. Marsh, 9/25/1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Dinner - Thirteenth Annual Greater NY Union Label Awards of Merit to Harry Lorber and Martin Dash, 9/24/1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Union Label Exhibit Show, Utica, NY, 1954, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Exposition - Montreal, Canada, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Freedomland, August 1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Labor Hero Award, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (4th), 1958 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (5th), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (6th-Albany), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (7th-Jamestown), 1961 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (8th-Rochester), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (9th-Syracuse), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (10th-NYC), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit ( 11th-Buffalo), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit ( 12th-NYC), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Labor -Management Exhibit (13th-Westbury, LI ), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (14th-Rochester), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (15th-NYC), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit ( 16th-Albany), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (17th-Rochester), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (18th-NYC), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (19th-Uniondale, LI ), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (20th-Syracuse), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (21st-Buffalo), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (23rd-Rochester), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Labor - Management Exhibit (NYC), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Miss Union Maid - Semifinalists, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Miss Union Maid - Applicants, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Miss Union Maid Doll, 1960s, early 1970s (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Musical Activities - American Union Chorus & Duo-Pianists, 1964, 1965, 1967, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - National Electrical Week, 1968, 1969, 1971, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Parade With NYS AFL Convention in NYC (Newspaper- Clippings), 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Parade With NYS AFL Convention, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Parade - Labor Day (Awards Committee), 1960, 1961, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Pete the Pup, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt Raceway, 1959-60, 1966, 1968-70, 1972, 1974-6 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Salute to Labor - Baseball Doubleheader, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Service Award in Journalism - Greater NY & LI Union Label and Service Trade Council, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Spartacus Promotional, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Testimonials For Labor Leaders, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Union Label Week, 1950, 1951, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Union Label Week - Proclamations, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Union Label Week, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Union Label Week, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Union Label Week, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Union Label Week, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Union Label Week, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Union Label Week, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Union Label Week, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Union Label Week, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Union Label Week, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Union Label Week, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Union Label Week, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Union Label Week, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Union Label Week, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - The Union Shopper, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Union Showtime, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Union Vacation, 1966, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Yonkers Raceway, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Series X: Subject Files, 1947-1979
  The subject files encompass both issues of importance to the Union Label Trades as well as other organizations with which the union label organizations were involved. Major subject files include strikes-boycotts­ demonstrations (Coors boycott, Burke-Hartke Save Jobs Rally-1972, Judy Bond boycott, Farah strike and boycott), copies of contracts containing language on the union label. Types of material include pamphlets, news releases, flyers, programs, correspondence and certificates.
  - Air Force A-X Contract, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) - Union Label, 1962-64, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1952-1954 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - AFL-CIO Jobs And Trade Legislative Newsletter, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - AFL-CIO News Service, 1963, 1965-67, 1970, 1972-75 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Boycott - Coors Beer, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Boycott List, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Boycott - United Farm Workers, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Boycott - Van Heusen, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Brooklyn Labor Lyceum, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Burke - Hartke Save Jobs Rally, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - "Buy American" Campaign, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - "Buy Union - Buy Ansco (Film)", 1962 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Central Trades and Labor Council Announcements with Sinnigen on Executive Board, 1945-1949 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Certificates of Appreciation to Harry Avrutin, 1951, 1959, 1966, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Contract - Union Label Contract Language, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Directory of AFL Union Products and Services, 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Imports Issue, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Imports Issue - Anti-Import Testimony before U.S. Tariff Commission by Joseph Tuvim, not dated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Imports Issue - Pocketbook, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1963, 1965, 1973, not dated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Labeling - Textile Shrinkage, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Labor's League For Political Education - NYS, 1947-48, 1956-57 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - New York State Federation of Labor, 1954-1958 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Office Employees International Union - Local 153, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s, 1970s (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Other Union Label Organizations, (Alabama, Los Angeles), not dated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Reception At Union Industries Information Center Honoring S. Talarico and E. McDavid, 9/27/1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Reports to NYS AFL-CIO by Union Label And Services Trade Department, 1967, 1969, 1972, 1974-76, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Sources for Union Products - List, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Strike - Farah Pants, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Strike - Judy Bond Blouses, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Strike - Kingsport Press, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Strike - Oneita, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Strike, Boycott, Correspondence, Announcements, 1958, 1960s, 1970s (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Talarico, Sam, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Tri-County Labor-Management Institute (Hofstra University), 1963-65, 1967-68 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Union Label Agreements, not dated (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Series XI: Publications, 1951-1976
  - Buyers Guide - Official Directory NYS AFL-CIO Union Products and Services, ULSTD of NYS, 1959, 1966-1970, 1974, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department News, ULSTD of NYS, Includes special convention roundup issues and labor-management exhibit issues. (transferred to Tamiment's serials collection), 1960-1976 (Box 15)
  - Union Label Trades News and Directory, ULSTD of NYS, 1946-1949 (Box 15)
  - ULST Council of Greater NY and Long Island - press releases, 1954-1972 (Box 15)
  - ULST Council of Greater NY and Long Island - announcements, 1951-1974 (Box 15)
- Series XII: Accretion, 1942-1993
  - Materials from the 22nd (1990), 64th (1991), 65th (1992) and 66th (1993) annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, responses and letters to address; CCL Affiliations memos; Memos and planning files for the 1987 Beef Packers reception; history of union labels; 1978 New York State Green Book buyers guide, 1975-1991 (Box 16)
  - Materials from the 30th (1984) annual convention including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, letters to address and related program materials (Box 17)
  - Materials from the 58th (1985) and 60th (1987), annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, memos, and letters to address; "Dollar and Sense" newsletter; Union Label Square dedication photographs, 1969-1987 (Box 18)
  - Materials from the 53rd (1980), 58th (1985), 59th (1986) and 60th (1987) annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, letters to address and related program materials; Correspondence 1940s-1960s; Union Label promotional materials, 1942-1987 (Box 19)
  - Materials from the 54th (1981), 55th (1982), 56th (1983) and 56th (1984) annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, letters to address and related program materials; "Union Consumer"; undated convention photographs, 1981-1984 (Box 20)
  - Materials from the 60th (1987), 61st (1988), and 62nd (1989) annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, letters to address and related program materials; photographs from the 60th annual convention; Report of officers roundup 1981-1987, 1981-1989 (Box 21)
  - Materials from the 63rd (1990), 64th (1991), 65th (1992) and 66th (1993) annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, responses and letters to address; Programs from the 61st, 63rd, 65th and 66th annual conventions, 1988-1993 (Box 22)
  - Labor Management Exhibit correspondence, 1965-1977; Council Meeting notices; ULSTD Emergency Meeting Notes; Department minutes, 1988-1993; Bottle bills correspondence; Photographs of Council Executive Board; 23rd Annual Labor Management Exhibit (Rochester, NY); Releases and letters; 1980 Council meetings and letters, 1962-1993 (Box 23)
  - Materials from the 63rd (1990), 65th (1992) and 66th (1993) annual conventions including committee minutes, event programs, planning notes, responses and letters to address; Union Industries Information Committee (UIIC) photographs; Union Label and Services Trade Council golden anniversary program; Coors Brewing Company boycott correspondence and press clippings; "Empire State Report" newsletter; 1985-1991 correspondence, 1962-1993 (Box 24)